

# Jorge Aliaga Luque Software Developer

LinkedIn Profile

jorgealiaga36@gmail.com +34 674 745 883 Barcelona, Spain

https://jorgealiaga36.github.io/jorge-aliaga-luque/

# **Work Experience**



# INDRA | Computer Vision Developper Oct 2022 - Present

- Development, fine tuning and training of different ATDR models (Automatic Detection and Recognition) for the NGWS/FCAS (fighter aircraft design).
- Thermal camera software video capturing and integration into computer vision models.
- Development of image stitching algorithms with their corresponding pre and post processing techniques.
- Building and labeling datasets.



# INDRA | Embedded Software Developper Oct 2021 - Oct 2022

- Resolution of incidents in embedded C++ software in the naval IRST F-110 defense project.
- Development of an HMI tool for the management and maintenance o surveillance system.
- Integration and testing of hardware components.



#### PLC Programmer | DEUSER

(Feb 2021 - Mar 2021)

- Programming of PLC's in TIA Portal (Siemens).
- KUKA robotics programming via WorkVisual.

# **Education**



Erasmus + | Budapest University of Technology and Economics

(Sep 2020 - Feb 2021)



# Bachelor in Industrial Electronics and Automation | Carlos III University of Madrid

(2016 - 2021)

- Digital analogic and power electronics.
- Embedded software (C / C++).
- Control engineering.
- Robotics programming (C++ / RAPID).

# **Profile**

Electronics and automation engineer with experience in computer vision and embedded software development through participation in defense projects. Hard-working and decisive person with strong interest in Data Science and machine learning with a desire to train in this field at a professional level.

## **Skills**



### Image Processing

# Languages

#### **Spanish**

(Native)

#### **English**

(B2)

#### Courses

- Machine Learning Specialization (Coursera)
- Deep Learning Specialization (Coursera)
- Optoelectronics and Applications (University of Alcalá, Madrid)